<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hard Rolls</title>
      <link>/hard-rolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 21:16:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hard-rolls/</guid>
      <description>Hard Rolls / Brötchen A German classic - Brötchen! The secret to very good ones is time. My Sunday brötchen I start already on Friday. Also important is a &amp;ldquo;Poolish&amp;rdquo;, a pre-ferment - made from just flour and water in a 1:1 ratio, and a tiny bit yeast.
 Let&amp;rsquo;s start&amp;hellip;. How many Brötchen you want to make? pcs. Single weight (typically 80g) g Flour is always 100%  Water (may need to adjust to your flour) % Salt (standard 2%) % Yeast (typically 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brian&#39;s Baguette</title>
      <link>/brians-baguette/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brians-baguette/</guid>
      <description>Brian&#39;s Baguettes There are many baguette recipes only, many bad ones, many good ones. From the many good ones I picked Brian&amp;rsquo;s. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, straight forward, and most importantly it makes really good baguettes!
Some notes from my side=&amp;gt; The poolish is essential! The poolish will give you the amazing taste. The water content you really need to ajust to your flour! 1% can make a difference. Very soft/sticky dough is not nice to work with and can be very difficult to shape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brötchen</title>
      <link>/broetchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/broetchen/</guid>
      <description>Brötchen So mache ich derzeit meine klassischen Brötchen. Das Geheimrezept dabei ist Zeit. Die Sonntagsbrötchen fange ich schon am Freitag an. Auch wichtig ist ein &amp;ldquo;Poolish&amp;rdquo; - ein Vorteig aus Mehl, Wasser im Verhältnis 1:1 und ganz wenig Hefe.
 Also los geht&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;. Wie viele Brötchen sollen es werden? Stück Einzelgewicht (normal 80g) g Mehl ist immer 100%  Wasser (da muss man sich hinloten) % Salz (Standart 2%) % Hefe (normal 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Pizza Pizza!</title>
      <link>/pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 23:10:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pizza/</guid>
      <description>Pizza Calculator Here is your pizza dough calculator for Neapolitan style hand shaped pizza.
The recipe will adjust depending on how many pizza you plan to make, and how much gram dough per piece. For a ⌀~25-30cm/10-12&amp;quot; pizza I typically use 250g.
After you put the dough in the fridge you can leave it there for a few days. Taste is getting better after 1 day, 1-3 days is the optimum.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
